Rahat Ansari

Software Engineer

Ramjanpur Jamadoba., Dhanbad, Jharkhand, India, 828301

+91 8210962581

rahatansari933@gmail.com

Specializing in software engineering and ui developer Knowledge, seeks to create convenient interfaces that fulfill the user's needs design and web technologies. I can learn something new and also utilize my skill in progress.

I believe in team work, time management and I think that my motto is that "Good can be Groomed ".

Professional Experience

Axiever Pvt.Ltd

February 2023 - Present

UI Developer / Front-End Developer

- Testing new designs on mobile and desktop Responsive
- Visualising interactive elements, like buttons, sliders, toggles, icons, drop-down menus, and text fields
- Analysing the impact of design and usability changes
- Problem-solving skills
- · Assisted in creating the overall look and feel of the application, modifying code as needed

Uinfotechnology Pvt.Ltd, Dhanbad

March 2022 - February 2023

Web Developer

- · Developed and maintained websites for multiple organizations using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Analyze user needs to determine technical requirements
- Design and establish user friendly website and also establish an interactive and dynamic website
- Maintain and update websites based on feedback from clients

SB-Creation Pvt Ltd, Kolkata

December 2021 - April 2022

Frontend Developer (Training / Internship)

- Developed frontend code for web applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Collaborated with backend developers to create a dynamic web experience
- Responsible for creating responsive web designs that worked across various browsers
- Develop databases that support web applications and websites

Education

IES Institute Of Technology And Management at Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh

Bachelor Of Technology in Computer Science Engineering August 2017 - June 2021

C.S College at Belhar, Bihar

Intermediate in Science June 2015 - May 2017

S B High School at Bhaga, Dhanbad

Secondary in Matric May 2012 - April 2014

Key Skills

- Html & Css
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- PHP
- MySql

Languages

- Hindi
- English

Interests

- Travelling
- Gaming